[
    {
        "title" : "Who Am I?"
    },


    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "I am the leading scorer in Football World Cup History with 16 goals.",
      "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "I've starred in many Tarantino Films, portraying characters such as Hans Landa and Dr. King Schultz.",
        "answer": "Christoph Waltz"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I'm a Barbadian singer whose debut album was called Music of the Sun",
        "answer": "Rihanna"
      },
      {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "I was the first Vice-President of the United States to become President.",
          "answer": "John Adams"
      },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Alongside my brother Kimbal, my first main business venture was creating Zip2 which was an Internet City guide with maps, directions and Yellow Pages.",
        "answer": "Elon Musk"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I'm the current 9th in line to the British Throne and My husband is a property developer.",
        "answer": "Princess Beatrice"
      },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "I was a novelist, playwrite and poet, best known for my debut novel, The Lord of the Flies.",
        "answer": "William Golding"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "I was the founder of North Korea.",
        "answer": "Kim Il Sung"
      },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "I  was an Italian sculptor, painter, architect and poet, whose famous works include The Madonna of the Stairs and David.",
        "answer": "Michelangelo"
      },
      {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "I was appointed the Supreme Allied Commander of the Allied Expeditionary Force during World War II.",
          "answer": "General Dwight D. Eisenhower"
      }
]
  